radioplanet.tv 2012-06-21

# Privacy | RadioPlanet.tv | Where Hip Hop Meets Hollywood

**Updated: April 20, 2012**

We value your privacy, and we want to help make your experience with RadioPlanet as satisfying and safe as possible. We have established this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect Personal Information (as defined below), and how we use and disclose that Personal Information. “Personal Information,” as used in this Privacy Policy, is information that allows a person to directly identify an individual, such as name or email address, and information that we combine directly with such identifying information. By using the site, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Like most web-based services, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser. We may use a variety of methods, including clear GIFs (also known as “web beacons”), and “cookies” to collect this information. The information that we collect with these automated methods may include, for example, your IP address, a unique device or user ID, browser type, system type, the content and pages that you access, and the “referring URL”.

We use passively-collected information to administer, operate, and improve the site and our other services and systems, and to provide services and content that are tailored to you, including providing customized advertisements and monitoring and reporting of the effectiveness of marketing campaigns. If we directly combine any information gathered through passive means with Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, we use information collected by passive means in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable forms.

Websites visited before visiting may place Personal Information within the URL of your browser during a visit to that previous website. We may unintentionally collect that information as part of referring URL information that it collects.

Also, please be aware that other third parties, including advertising servers, advertising networks, Third Party Application Developers, may set cookies or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of their services. We do not have access to, or control over, these cookies or other means of passive data collection. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these Third Party Application Developers, Network Creators, advertising servers or advertising networks. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers, Third Party Application Developers or websites.

## Third Party Advertisers

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, such as Google AdSense, to serve advertisements. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear automatically receive your IP Address and other log file information when this happens. Such third-party companies may also use other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. Certain third-party companies, such as Google, may also use these cookies to serve ads to you based on your visit to these Ning Networks and other sites on the Internet.

We do not provide your Personal Information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience that they were trying to reach.

You may click here to visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, where you can learn more about its member companies’ practices and to opt out from the collection and use of information by its member companies.

Additionally, if any Google AdSense advertisements are used, you may opt out of Google’s use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy located here.

We reserve the right to add or remove third-party ad networks and ad servers in our discretion. We may not at all times list such updated ad network or ad server partners in this Privacy Policy.

## Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of your Personal Information, including email addresses, to that entity. We will use reasonable efforts to notify registered users of such a transfer (by a posting on our home page, or by email, as chosen by us in our discretion).

## Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of Personal Information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to maintain the security of such Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that it will remain free from unauthorized access, use, disclosure, or alteration. Further, while we work hard to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent “hackers” or other unauthorized persons from illegally accessing or obtaining this information. We do not assume any liability to third parties whose information you include in your Address Book, or which you post or transmit.

## Children

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online privacy of children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under the age of 13, unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides Personal Information represents to us that he or she is 13 years of age or older. If we learn that Personal Information has been collected from a user under 13 years of age then we will take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted.

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your children’s access to certain types of material on the Internet. While we do not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service to our community.

  * ConnectSafely
  * The Family Online Safety Institute
  * iKeepSafe
  * OnGuard Online, maintained by the Federal Trade Commission
  * Netsmartz.org
  * The Child Safety Network
  * Cyber Sitter
  * Common Sense Media
  * WebWiseKids.org
  * Center for Safe and Responsible Internet Use
  * Cyber Angels
  * Cyber Bullying US

## International Users

Our site is hosted in the United States. If you use the site from the European Union, or any other region with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States. The United States does not have the same data protection laws as the European Union and other regions. By providing Personal Information under this Privacy Policy, you consent to the use of Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the transfer of your Personal Information to the United States.

## Changes and Updates to This Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will update the “effective date” at the top of the Privacy Policy. If we make an update to this Privacy Policy that is materially less restrictive in our use or disclosure of Personal Information that we collected prior to the update, we will provide you with prior notice of the pending update and seek your consent by posting notice here. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about our collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information on the the site. Your continued use of radioplanet.tv constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

## Contacting Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at admin@radioplanet.tv.
